<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sydney Tour</string>

    <!--Parks-->
    <string name="description_hyde_park">Hyde Park is a heritage-listed 16.2-hectare urban park located in the central
        business district of Sydney, in the City of Sydney local government area of New South Wales, Australia, Hyde
        Park is the oldest public parkland in Australia.</string>

    <string name="description_bicentennial_park">Bicentennial Park is a 40-hectare of parkland located 16 kilometres west 
        of the Sydney central business district in the local government area of City of Parramatta. Bicentennial 
        Park is situated on the shores Homebush Bay and is a part of the Sydney Olympic Park in New South Wales, Australia.</string>

    <string name="description_sydney_park">Sydney Park is a large recreational area in the inner-city area of Sydney,
        New South Wales, Australia. The parkland is located at St Peters, sitting along the borders of Alexandria,
        Newtown and Erskineville. Sydney Park is 41.6 hectares in area, which makes it the third largest park in inner-city Sydney.</string>

    <string name="description_blaxland_riverside_park">Blaxland Riverside Park is a great new space in Sydney Olympic Park,
        with an excellent play area and plenty of activities on offer for the whole family. Whether you’re more into having
        a relaxing family picnic, or going on a long adventurous bike ride, the Blaxland Riverside Park is the perfect place
        for your next weekend outing with the little ones.
    </string>

    <string name="description_harbour_nation_park">The Sydney Harbour National Park is an Australian national park comprising
        parts of Port Jackson, Sydney and its foreshores and various islands. The 392-hectare national park lies in
        New South Wales and was created progressively, from 1975.</string>

    <!--Restaurants-->
    <string name="description_arya_restaurant">Chef Matt Moran presents Modern Australian haute cuisine in an elegant, glass-walled dining room.</string>
    <string name="description_restaurant_hubert">Hubert is a French restaurant located in the heart of downtown Sydney.
        We are open for lunch Thursday to Friday, and dinner through to late night supper Monday to Saturday.</string>
    <string name="description_bennelong_restaurant">Bennelong serves to celebrate the Sydney Opera House
        and its extraordinary architecture by offering a culturally significant
        and inspiring menu showcasing a most magnificent production of Australian food and wine.</string>
    <string name="description_tetsuyas_restaurant">An art-filled house overlooking a Japanese garden,
        offering an acclaimed French-Asian tasting menu.</string>
    <string name="description_mr_wong_restaurant">Modern Cantonese menu, from dim sum to classic mud crab, served in a lavish French-colonial setting.</string>


    <!--Museums-->
    <string name="description_museum_of_sydney">The Museum of Sydney is a historical collection and exhibit,
        built on the ruins of the house of New South Wales\' first Governor,
        Arthur Phillip, on the present-day corner of Phillip and Bridge Street, Sydney.</string>
    <string name="location_museum_of_sydney">Bridge St &amp; Phillip St, Sydney NSW 2000</string>
    <string name="description_australian_museum">The Australian Museum is a heritage-listed museum at 1 William Street,
        Sydney central business district, New South Wales, Australia. It is the oldest museum in Australia, with an 
        international reputation in the fields of natural history and anthropology.</string>
    <string name="location_australian_museum">1 William St, Sydney NSW 2010</string>

    <string name="description_hydepark_museum">The Hyde Park Barracks, Sydney is a heritage-listed former barracks,
        hospital, convict accommodation, mint and courthouse and now museum and cafe located at Macquarie Street
        in the Sydney central business district, in the City of Sydney local government area of New South Wales,
        Australia.</string>
    <string name="location_hydepark_museum">Queens Square, Macquarie St, Sydney NSW 2000</string>
    <string name="description_susannah_museum">Susannah Place is a heritage-listed former grocery store and workers\'
        cottages and now historic house museum located at 58-64 Gloucester Street in the inner city Sydney
        suburb of The Rocks in the City of Sydney local government area of New South Wales, Australia.
        It was built during 1844.</string>
    <string name="location_susannah_museum">58/64 Gloucester St, The Rocks NSW 2000</string>
    <string name="description_powerhouse_museum">The Powerhouse Museum is the major branch of the Museum of Applied
        Arts &amp; Sciences in Sydney, the other being the historic Sydney Observatory.</string>
    <string name="location_powerhouse_museum">500 Harris St, Ultimo NSW 200</string>

    <string name="description_australian_maritime_museum">The Australian National Maritime Museum is a federally 
        operated maritime museum in Darling Harbour, Sydney</string>
    <string name="location_australian_maritime_museum">2 Murray St, Sydney NSW 2000</string>

    <!--Landmarks-->
    <string name="sydney_tour_eye">Sydney Tower Eye</string>
    <string name="description_sydney_tour_eye">Landmark building, opened in 1981, with a 4-D cinema,
        observation deck and outdoor viewing platform.</string>
    <string name="location_sydney_tour_eye">100 Market St, Sydney NSW 2000</string>

    <string name="circular_quay">Circular Quay</string>
    <string name="description_circular_quay">Circular Quay is a harbour, former working port and now international 
        passenger shipping port, public piazza and tourism precinct, heritage area, and 
        transport node located in Sydney</string>
    <string name="location_circular_quay">Sydney central business district</string>

    <string name="sydney_opera_house">Sydney Opera House</string>
    <string name="description_opera_house">The Sydney Opera House is a multi-venue performing arts centre at Sydney Harbour
        in Sydney, New South Wales, Australia. It is one of the 20th century\'s most famous and distinctive buildings.</string>
    <string name="location_opera_house">Bennelong Point, Sydney NSW 2000</string>

    <string name="sydney_harbour_bridge">Sydney Harbour Bridge</string>
    <string name="description_sydney_harbour_bridge">The Sydney Harbour Bridge is a heritage-listed steel through arch
        bridge across Sydney Harbour that carries rail, vehicular, bicycle, and pedestrian traffic between the Sydney
        central business district and the North Shore.</string>
    <string name="location_sydney_harbours_bridge">Sydney Harbour Bridge, Sydney NSW, Australia</string>

    <string name="taronga_zoo_sydney">Taronga Zoo Sydney</string>
    <string name="description_taronga_zoo_sydney">Taronga Zoo Sydney is a zoo located in Sydney, New South Wales,
        Australia in the suburb of Mosman, on the shores of Sydney Harbour. It was officially opened on 7 October 1916.</string>
    <string name="location_taronga_zoo_sydney">Bradleys Head Road, Mosman, Sydney</string>

</resources>
